我刚刚瞟到了机长
Hey -- I just caught a glimpse of our pilot,
他长得和萨利机长一模一样
and he looks exactly like Sully.
美国英雄机长  他的故事在2016年还翻拍了电影
我觉得就是萨利机长本人
I-I think it is Sully.
我记得机长好像是个女的
I think that's a woman.
-才不是  -是的
- No, it's a -- ‭- Yeah.
我知道你的小算盘
Oh, I know what you're doing,
你在测试我有多支持女权主义
you're testing the limits of my feminism.
告诉你吧
I will have you know that
原创翻译  双语字幕
我完全能接受我的生命
I am perfectly fine putting my life in the hands
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
掌握在女性飞行员手中
of a female pilot.
翻译:  glida    Eunice油腻希
■
各位旅客们好  我是你们的机长
Hi, folks. This is your captain.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
本航班将于6小时24分钟后
Our flight time to Turks and Caicos
翻译:  洗七里   狂风暴雨赛太公
抵达特克斯和凯科斯群岛[中美洲]
is six hours, 24 minutes.
各乘务人员  准备起飞
Flight attendants, prepare for takeoff.
好了
All right.
校对:  挥别红V赛太公
该吃罗纳多专门给咱在航班上吃的药了
‭Time to take that special flying medicine Ronaldo gave us.
是啊  这个"库达多"是什么意思
Yes, what does "Cuidado" mean?
好像是"安眠"的意思
I think it means "Sleep tight"?
Cuidado实为西语"警告"的意思
时间轴:  三水
-我也不知道  -好吧  一口闷
- I don't know. - ‭Oh, well, cheers!
祝您安眠
Cuidado.‭
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
好啦
Okay.
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
■
什么情况
What happened?
我们已经降落了吗
Did we land?
这药效果也太好了
Oh, man, that stuff is good.
旅客们  我有个坏消息
Bad news, folks,
发生了一些机械故障
we have some mechanical issues.
我们需要返回登机口
We need to head back to the gate.
每当听到返回登机口
Okay, any time you head back to the gate,
就表示你航班不会起飞
that means your flight's not taking off.
好吧  拿好行李
All right, gather your things.
淘宝搜索店铺：我爱美剧创意周边
我们得赶紧换个航班
We're gonna need to scramble to find another one.
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十八集
五分钟可以发生许多事
普里契特先生  五分钟后
Okay, Mr. Pritchett, there is a connecting flight
有一趟在达拉斯转机的航班
through Dallas that leaves in five minutes.
如果二位尽快的话可以赶上
You can catch it if you hurry.
可我不想去达拉斯
I don't want to go to Dallas.
我们要去的是特克斯和凯科斯群岛
We're going to Turks and Caicos.
您在达拉斯转机而已
Dallas is just where you make your connection.
不好意思  我的大脑
I'm sorry, I'm having a really hard time
现在处理不了任何信息
processing information right now.
我们吃了安眠药
We took sleeping pills.
你们只要去32号登机口就好
Just make your way over to gate 32.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
我去
I can- wow.
等等  机票上怎么写着"达拉斯"
Wait, why do these say "Dallas"?
-我不知道  -女士
- I have no idea. ‭- Ma'am?
抱歉  我们遇到了严重问题
Sorry, there's been a horrible mistake.
我们想去的不是达拉斯
We don't want to go to Dallas.
好吧
Okay.
仔细听好  你们是在达拉斯转机
Listen carefully -- you're connecting in Dallas
到特克斯和凯科斯群岛
to Turks and Caicos.
你们要在4分钟内赶到32号登机口
You need to be at gate 32 in four minutes,
明白吗
do you understand?
当然  我又不是白痴
Yes. I'm not an idiot.
好  我们要在32分钟内赶到4号登机口
Okay, we have to be at gate 4 in 32 minutes.
错了  是32号登机口  写手上
No, gate 32, write it down.
写就写
Okay.
她哪来这么大火气
Why is she so angry?
这不明摆着的吗  她对我有意思
Isn't it obvious? She's totally into me.
-不然怎么白送我记号笔  -有道理
- She gave me a marker. - Mmm! Makes sense.
-走着  -走着
- All right. ‭- Okay.
-我就跟着你走了  -走着
- I'm just gonna follow you. - Okay. ‭Yeah.
走错了
Wrong!
我就知道  我直觉可准了
I knew it. Instinct.
-走着  -等等  不  我的包呢
- Okay, yes. ‭- Wait, no, my bag.
-我的包不见了  -好吧
- My bag's gone. - ‭Okay, okay.
我的护照还在包里呢
It has my passport in it.
等等  那家伙  他偷了我的包
Wait, that guy -- he has my bag.
不好意思  先生
Excuse me, sir.
想偷我的包没那么容易
Nice try stealing my bag.
你居然已经把包涂成别的颜色了
I see you've already painted it.
小卡  包又出现在你肩膀上了
Cam, it-it's back on your shoulder!
我的天  你可真是神乎其技
Oh, my God. You are good.
小卡  听我说听我说
Cam, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me.
如果我们想平安抵达达拉斯
If we're gonna have any chance of getting to Dallas
并在那幸存下去  我们需要帽子
and then surviving there, we are going to need hats.
帽子
Hats.
不好意思  先生先生先生
Excuse me, sir, sir, sir, sir,
您是这间帽子小铺的业主吗
are you the proprietor of this haberdashery?
你能够告诉我你店里
Can you point me in the direction
最好的体育鸭舌帽吗
of your finest sports caps?
哪个队的
What team?
"为哪个队效力"常指性向是弯还是直
弯的  我不知道这和买帽子有什么关系
Gay -- I'm not sure why that's relevant.
你怎么这样
Oh. Okay.
我还是
I'll just --
我也有个问题想问你
Yeah, I have a question for you.
你不上班的时候也戴帽子吗
When you're outside the workplace, do you wear hats?
还是那样会让你觉得
Or does that just kind of make you feel
你一直在上班
like you're always in the office?
这样吧  这些我全要了
Oh, you know what, I think I am going to get these.
不行  米奇尔  我们不能
No, Mitchell, we can't --
看啊  小女孩戴的帽子
Oh, look, little girls' hats.
我们应该给琳达买一顶
Ooh. We should get one for Linda.
-那是谁  -我们的女儿啊
- Who? - ‭Um, our daughter?
-不  她叫莉莉  -我喜欢那个名字
- No, it's Lily. - Oh, I love that name.
米奇尔  你胳膊上怎么写着32
Mitchell, why do you have 32 written on your arm?
我不知道
I have no idea.
或许是什么密码  或许是我的年纪
Maybe it's some sort of code, or maybe it's my age.
你觉得我看起来像32岁吗
Do I look 32 to you?
实话实说  不  不要说实话
Tell me the truth. No, you know what -- don't.
如果我们写在手上  那肯定是很重要的事
Well, if we wrote it down, it must be something important.
我们该把其他看起来
Hey, we should write down other stuff
很重要的事也写下来  以免忘了
that seems important so we don't forget.
对  好的
Yeah, okay.
帽子
Um, well, hats.
-帽子  这是当然的  -当然的
- Hats, obviously. - Obviously.
好  还有什么
Okay. Ah, what else?
-我记得还有个什么  -一个数字
- I feel like there was a -- - A number.
-是32  -32
- there was -- 32. - 32.
旅客们请注意
Attention, please.
米奇尔·普里契特与卡梅隆·塔克
Passengers Mitchell Pritchett and Cameron Tucker...
-你也听到了吧  -听到了
- You're hearing that, right? - Yeah.
请立即到32号登机口登机
...please report to gate 32 immediately.
我们犯错误了吗
Are we in trouble?
-我不知道  -他听起来很生气
- I don't know. - He sounds mad.
是很生气  你看
He does. Hey.
不不不
No, no, no.
不不不  小卡  不要
No, no, no. Cam, don't.
你敢
Don't you dare.
不  椅子看起来太舒服太有诱惑力了
No, I -- they just look so soft and inviting.
我觉得我坚持不住了
I-I don't think I can go on.
告诉琳达我爱她
Tell Linda I love her.
不  你要挺过去亲口告诉她
No, you're gonna tell Linda yourself, okay?
没有你我在达拉斯怎么活
I cannot go to Dallas without you.
他们菜那么大份我自己吃会死
The portions there are so big.
我太累了  我实在太累了
I'm just so tired. I'm so very tired.
我眼睛都睁不开了
I just need to close my eyes.
少跟我来这套
Oh! ‭Knock it off!
你得忍住
Ow! ‭You're gonna suck it up.
你得打起精神来
You're gonna pull your act together.
你得跟我去3232号登机口
And you're coming with me to gate 3232.
这号码不对吧
That can't be right.
我们永远到不了
We're just never gonna make it.
我的天  你说得对
Oh, my God. You're right.
我们会死在这个机场的
We're gonna die in this airport.
这是去达拉斯的224航班
This is the final boarding call
在32号登机口的最后登机通知
for flight 224 to Dallas at gate 32.
等等  我们还赶得及  英雄请留步
Wait, there's still time. Sir, stop!
停车
Stop!
请问您能不能载我们去
Is there a way that you can take us
-32号登机口  -32号  没错
- to gate 32? ‭- 32, yeah.
-好吧  -好
- I guess. ‭- Okay, wow.
太感谢您了  您救了我们的命
Thank you so much. You are a life saver.
麻烦您快点
Please hurry. Okay.
到了
We're here.
-谢谢您  -太感谢您了
- Thank you. - ‭Oh, thank you.
-万分感谢  -万分感谢
- Thank you so much. - Thank you so much.
我们是米奇和小卡
Mitch and Cam.
您好  我们是米奇和小卡
Hi! ‭Hi! ‭Hi, we're Mitch and Cam!
我是米奇  他是小卡
I'm Mitch, he's Cam.
塔克先生  普里契特先生
Mr. Tucker, Mr. Pritchett --
你们刚好赶到
you made it just in time.
太好了  我的天
Okay. Oh, my gosh.
谢谢二位
Thank you.
露西  我们女儿的名字叫露西
Lucy, her name is Lucy.
我们回家来了  露西
We're coming home, Lucy!
各位  我们五分钟后
Hey, everyone, we are firing up the hologram
向进取号星舰发射全息图
to the Starship Enterprise in five minutes.
不来是傻子
Be there or be square.
我觉得去了也是傻子
I don't think he had to "or" that one.
亲爱的  现在我们到这里了
You know, honey, now that we're here,
我不确定擅自来找艾丽克斯是个好主意
I'm not sure it's such a great idea to barge in on Alex.
克莱尔  我担心她
Claire, I'm worried.
她不回我们短信
She's not returning texts.
她朋友说她从不出门
Her friend says she never goes out.
一生频道里讲到大学女生崩溃的电影中
This is the first act of every Lifetime movie
美国首个为女性设计的电视频道
都是以此为序幕
about college girl meltdowns.
好吧  但我们或许该先跟她说一下
Yeah, but maybe we should give her a little head's up.
在"全优生到全忧生"中
That's what Alicia Silverstone's mom, Judith Light,
该频道只有一部《全优生到女优生》
艾丽西娅·希尔维斯通与朱迪斯·萊特皆是名演员
艾丽西亚的妈妈朱迪斯一开始也这么觉得
thought in "From Straight A's to a Straight Jacket."
相信我  这是确保她没有
‭Trust me, this is the best way to make sure
晚上躲起来抑郁的最好方式
she's not spending her nights holed up and depressed.
艾丽克斯  宝贝  爸妈来了
Alex? Honey, it's Mom and Dad.
或许这是好现象
Oh, well, maybe this is a good sign.
或许她已经和朋友出去了  就像正常...
Maybe she's already out with friends, just like a normal --
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
想着来打声招呼  或许带你出去吃顿饭
Thought we'd pop by, say hi, maybe take you out for a bite.
除非你已经和一群有趣的人约好出去吃饭了
Unless you've already got fun group dinner plans?
我的玉米卷饼热好了
My burrito's ready.
你在喝酒吗
You're drinking?
有时酒能帮助我睡眠
Wine helps me sleep sometimes.
我真希望你们先打电话通知我
You know, I really wish you guys had called.
我现在忙着课业什么的
I'm so busy with school stuff right now,
这里也一团乱
and this place is a mess.
你在这里啊
Aww, there you are.
你买了猫吗
You got a cat?
-不是我的  -你偷了一只猫吗
- It's not mine. - You stole a cat?
就像"耶鲁生沦落监狱"的内芙·坎贝尔
Just like Neve Campbell in "From Yale to Jail."
有这本书但没这部剧
内芙·坎贝尔是知名电视女演员
老天  宝贝  你真的没事吗
Oh, God. Honey, are you sure you're okay?
这是周六晚上
It's Saturday night.
你却穿着浴袍在喝酒
You're drinking wine in your bathrobe
还有一只来路不明的猫
with a come-from-nowhere cat.
这有什么问题吗
What's wrong with that?
不算猫的话  我基本和你一模一样啊
Take away the cat, and I'm basically you.
宝贝
‭Honey,
我懂在大学格格不入是什么感觉
I know what it's like to be an outsider in college.
我和校园风云人物过去常在他们门口
The cool kids and I used to try to make them feel better
留香蕉面包以使他们感觉好点
by leaving banana bread outside their door.
我们先敲门  然后跑开藏在灌木丛后面
We'd knock and then run off and hide behind a bush
就为了看看他们脸上的表情
and watch them just to see the expression on their faces --
菲尔
Phil.
你爸和我只是很担心
Your dad and I are just concerned
因为你最近有点疏远了
'cause you've been so distant lately.
我跟你们说了我最近忙
I told you I've been busy.
没人说你的生活不精彩
Nobody's saying you don't lead a full life.
你学习  做玉米卷饼
You study, you make burritos.
或许你只是有点寂寞或忧郁
Maybe -- maybe you're just a little lonely or depressed.
妈  我很好
I'm fine, mom.
我们随时都能接你回去治疗
'Cause we could always get you back into therapy.
-没错  -或者让你搬回家和我们住
- Yes. - Or have you move home with us.
天  别说了
God, stop.
为什么你们总把我想成忧郁的废柴
Why do you guys always just assume I'm some depressed loser?
你们有没有想过我疏远了
Did it ever occur to you that maybe I've been so distant
是因为我忙着自己的生活
because I've been busy with my own life?
或许我活得很好
Maybe I'm doing great.
或许是因为我和一个特别的人在一起
Maybe I'm spending time with someone special.
她说得对
That's right.
本  你做什么呢
Ben, what are you doing?
我跟你说了待在里面
I told you to stay in there.
对不起  我以为你在铺哏要来个大揭秘
I'm sorry -- I thought you were, like, building to a big reveal.
我没有
I wasn't.
你和本...  亲爱的  他50岁了吧
You and Ben and -- Honey, isn't he 50?
他26岁
He's 26.
这是家族遗传
It runs in my family.
我直到死都会长这样
I'm gonna look like this until the day I die.
所以你是因为这个才不回家的啊
So, this is why you haven't been coming home?
因为你在和你妈的助理交往
You've been dating your mom's assistant?
我其实是营销经理
I'm actually a marketing manager.
知道吗  或许你围条毛巾
You know what? This might go better for everyone
对大家都好
if you throw a towel on.
好的  有道理
Okay, yeah. That makes sense.
克莱尔  你能别解雇我吗
Claire, co-- um, could you not fire me?
你们偷偷约会多久了
Ugh, how long have you two been sneaking around?
几个月吧
A couple of months.
我去圣地亚哥时我们分了段时间
We took a break when I went to San Diego.
-什么  有吗  -别...
- What? We did? - ‭Just...
这样可以吗
Is this okay?
当然  我们就是为它准备的
Um, yeah, yeah, we put it in for her.
-这是猫食玉米卷饼  -等等
- It's a feline burrito. - Wait a minute.
我就知道我认得这家伙
I knew I recognized that thing.
你应该知道  他带猫上班
You should know -- he brings that cat to work
现在看来  连约会也带
and apparently on dates.
他觉得是时候让他生命中
He thought it was time to bring together
最特别的两个女性见面了
the two most special ladies in his life.
我可受不了每天上班
Well, I cannot go to work every day
都要想他脸上为什么露出蠢笑
and wonder why he's got that stupid smile on his face.
怎么这都成你的事了
Why are you making this all about you?
这是我第一段成人关系  就这一段
‭This is the first adult relationship I've had in... ever.
但这是和本啊
But it's with Ben.
没事的  没事的  她没有恶意
‭It's okay. It's okay. She didn't mean that.
克莱尔  我能和你谈谈吗
Claire, can I talk to you for a second?
你可以在大家面前赞同我啊
Oh, you can agree with me in front of everyone.
我其实觉得你有点小题大做了
Actually, I think you're overreacting a little.
-什么  -我们来的时候以为
- What? - We came here thinking
我们女儿陷入某种抑郁中
our daughter was in some sort of a depression,
结果她恋爱了
and it turns out she's dating someone.
而且他其实挺讨喜且无害的
And he's actually pretty sweet and harmless.
你是这样吗  本  无害吗
Are you, Ben? Are you harmless?
请不要  不要
Please don't, don't.
他亲了我
He kissed me.
-你亲了我妈  -你亲了我老婆
- You kissed my mom?! - You kissed my wife?!
我以为我不亲就会丢了工作
Dude, I thought I had to or I would lose my job, okay?
-不是...  -这是真的
- That's not... - ‭That's for real.
我们当时加班  只有我们两个人
We were working late. It was just the two of us.
她伸手来拿春卷  大概吧
She reached over to grab a spring roll, I guess,
但她就停在我脸前  小声说着
but she got right in my face, and she whispered,
"妈妈饿了"
"Mmm, Mama's hungry."
克莱尔  我得说  这可能是你的错
I have to say, Claire, this one might be on you.
说得像我会滥用职权占你便宜
Like I would abuse my position to take advantage of you
而不是占仓库的托尼便宜
and not Tony from the warehouse?
-仓库的托尼是谁  -就是...
- Who's Tony from the warehouse? - Just...
那个吻真的是个误会
The kiss was an honest mistake.
或许吧  但还是有点怪
Maybe, but it was still a little off,
而本的大多事情都挺怪
like most things are with Ben.
或许我就喜欢有点怪的  而且他还有很多面
Maybe I like a little off. And that's not all he is.
他是个很棒的人  而且莫名懂我
He's an amazing person who somehow gets me.
他很体贴  也聪明
He's thoughtful and smart,
我感觉在他身边能做自己
and I feel like i can be myself around him.
而且他睡觉时鼻子会小小抽动
And his nose does this little wiggly thing when he sleeps.
你看我睡觉吗
You watch me sleep?
我也看你睡觉
Dude, I watch you sleep.
我真开心我们的关系曝光了
I'm really glad that this is finally out
我能告诉别人我对你的感觉了
and I can tell people how I feel about you.
我真的喜欢你  本
I really like you, Ben.
很喜欢
Like, a lot.
我从没爱别人像爱你一样深
And I have never loved anyone as much as you.
-别说着说着就怪了  -好吧
- Don't make this weird. - Oh, yeah.
她没有伤心寂寞
She's not sad and lonely.
-没有  但是更糟  -瞧瞧她  克莱尔
- No, it's so much worse. - Look at her, Claire.
你见过她这么开心吗
Have you ever seen her look so happy?
靠
Crap.
3  2  1
3, 2, 1.
-你抓的是我的手  本  -对不起
- That's my hand, Ben. - Oh, sorry.
我的错
‭My bad.
加速  曼尼
Speed it up, Manny.
电影还有五分钟就开场了
The movie starts in five minutes.
抱歉  但我是不会时速超过32公里的
Sorry, but I'm not going over 20 miles an hour
因为卡布奇诺咖啡机没系安全带
with this cappuccino machine not strapped in.
最新海外影视剧下载
一旦我练就了咖啡拉花技术
Once I perfect my foam art skills,
我的大一宿舍就是校园旺地了
my freshmen dorm will be the place to be.
我们可以再晚点跟他谈用"安全"措施了
I think we can put off that talk about using protection.
看  那里有一个车位
Mm, look, there's a spot right there.
看着悬  不过我还是试试吧
Looks tight, but I'll give it a try.
离路边太近了
You're too close to the curb.
要撞上了
You're gonna hit it.
我说什么来着
‭What'd I tell you?
没事的  乖儿子能做到
It's okay, Papi, you can do it.
绕过去
Go around.
有需要这样吗  你伸一根我还五根
Oh, really? Well, here's a bouquet of them!
好  我们再试一次
Okay, let's try this again.
够了  你下去  我来停车
Ugh, okay. Ah! Get out, I'll do it.
好"意外"哦
Surprise, surprise.
你刚刚说什么
What was that?
没什么  我是说我挺意外
Nothing, I was just saying that I am surprised
你像往常一样想要插手干涉
that you want to take over like you usually do.
-其实我不意外  -你这么指桑骂槐干嘛呢
- But I am not. - What are you cagey for?
我做错了什么
What did I do?
好吧  这个车位我停不进去
Okay, this spot's not happening.
我本来不想说的
Well, I didn't want to say anything,
但前几天  我们去杰夫和萨莉家时
but the other night, when we were at Jeff and Sally's,
我正在讲一个故事
I was in the middle of telling a story,
你就直接打断我  把结局说出来
you just took over and told the ending,
那样真的很没礼貌
and that was very rude.
这个车位好像不错  挺宽敞的
Okay, this one looks good -- It's huge.
你在气这个吗
That's what's bothering you?
我中途插入是为了救你
I jumped in to save you!
你都有点讲乱套
You were flailing.
快要被那些无关紧要的细节淹没了
You were drowning in a sea of unnecessary details.
怎么可能
‭Ah! How?!
我就喜欢那样说故事
That's the way I like to tell a story.
我喜欢巨细靡遗  更有画面感
I like to paint a picture.
讲故事就应该简短直接
A story should be short and simple.
不重要的细节不用告诉我
Don't tell me anything I don't need to know.
我是在带你踏上一段旅程
I am taking you on a journey.
而不是在教你如何组装书柜
I am not teaching you how to build a bookcase.
不是吧  你们明明看到我在等
Seriously? You saw me waiting.
就不能说一声你们不是要走吗
You couldn't tell me you weren't leaving?
你们记得自带购物袋
You brought your own shopping bags,
但却把礼貌忘在家里了
but you left your manners at home.
我只是想说  如果你想让故事好懂点
I'm just saying your story would be easier to follow
那就别一直讲岔题
if you didn't take so many side trips
并且再想想怎么架构你的故事
and you thought about the build a little bit.
你同意我说的吧  曼尼
You're with me on this, aren't you, Manny?
我喜欢妈妈说故事的方式
I like Mom's stories.
听到了没
See?
我就停这儿吧
I'm just gonna pull in here.
12块那么贵  难怪中产阶级那么愤怒
12 bucks? No wonder the middle class is so angry.
你绝对不可能听得懂她的故事
There's no way you would be able to follow her story.
他绝对听得懂
Yes, he would have.
好啊  你再说一遍
Fine. Tell it again.
几个礼拜前  我去逛超市
A couple of weeks ago, I go to the grocery store --
就是在华盛顿街
the one on Washington
右手边有个小小的红酒吧那一间
that has the tiny little wine bar to the right.
我进去后  就到处找纸巾
So, I come in, I'm looking for paper towels.
然后我想到  "我要犒劳一下自己
And I think, "Mmm, I'm gonna treat myself
喝点红酒吃点芝士"  有何不可呢
with some wine and some cheese." 'Cause why not?
于是我就去点了酒  然后我抬头时
So, I order my drink, and when I look up,
以为自己看到了桑德拉·布洛克
I thought I saw Sandra Bullock.
美国知名女演员  代表作有《生死时速》《地心引力》
停  你刚刚说
Stop. Right there,
你以为自己看到了桑德拉·布洛克
you just said you thought you saw Sandra Bullock.
我已经知道结局了  不是她
I already know the ending. It wasn't her.
故事结束
End of story.
对  但你还不知道其实是谁
Yeah, but you don't even know who it really was.
但我已经知道不是桑德拉·布洛克
But I know it's not Sandra Bullock,
所以我不感兴趣了
so I'm not invested.
我很喜欢她在《地心引力》里的表演
You know, I really loved her in that movie "Gravity."
谁在乎啊  她当时又不在场
Who cares? She wasn't there.
拜托你是真的要走
Oh, please be leaving.
我能说完我的故事吗
May I finish my story?
于是  我就跟着桑德拉·布洛克...
So, I start following Sandra Bullock...
不是桑德拉·布洛克
Not Sandra Bullock.
...逛超市
...around the grocery store.
她先去了冷冻区
She goes first to the frozen section,
然后去了清洁用品区
then she goes to the detergent aisle.
我一路上盘算着
I'm thinking to myself this whole time,
"我要去跟她打招呼
"I am gonna go and introduce myself,
但是一定要选对时机"
but it has to be at the right time."
于是我继续跟着她
So I keep following her.
最后  她离开超市
Eventually, she leaves the store.
她走出门  外面挺热的
She goes outside, which was actually really hot
虽然是一月份  记得吗  因为去年...
to be January, because, remember, last year --
我们知道是几月  我们知道天气
We know the month, we know the weather,
我们知道不是桑德拉·布洛克
we know it's not Sandra Bullock.
你要走了吗
Are you leaving?
我想要你的停车位
I want your spot.
拜托
Oh, please.
别往自己脸上贴金了  小姐
Don't flatter yourself, lady.
曼尼  你有在听吗
Manny, are you listening?
没有  对不起  我没注意
No, sorry. I wasn't paying attention.
因为你吸引不了他的注意力
Because you're not holding his attention.
这就是我一直在说的
And this is what I've been talking about --
多余的细节太多了
too many useless details.
说重点吧
Get on with it.
然后她转过身  摘掉墨镜
So, she turns around, she takes her sunglasses off,
真的很诡异
which was really weird,
因为那副墨镜居然跟我去年买的
because it was the exact same pair
后来落在飞机上的那副一模一样
that I bought last year that I lost on that plane ride --
没人在乎你的破墨镜
Nobody cares about your sunglasses.
直接说结尾吧
Just get to the end.
我现在不想说了
I don't want to now.
那个女人转过身对你妈妈说
The woman turns to your mother and says,
"天啊  你是莎尔玛·海雅克吗"
"Oh, my God. Are you Salma Hayek?"
墨西哥知名女星  代表作《弗里达》
有车位了
Here we go.
我只是想帮你
I'm just trying to help you.
打方向灯  看后视镜
Put on blinker, check mirrors,
注意抢停车位的混蛋
watch jerk steal your spot,
后悔四年级时就放弃练空手道了
regret quitting karate in 4th grade.
你知道吗  杰  重点不是
You know what, Jay, this is not about
谁的故事比较精彩
who tells the best story.
而是你那天晚上打断我
This is about you jumping in that night
好像你不希望我说下去
like you just wanted me to stop talking because
因为我让你丢脸了一样
I was embarrassing you or something.
你让我觉得自己好蠢
You made me feel stupid.
你觉得这没什么  但我觉得很受伤
You think it's nothing, but you hurt my feelings.
歌洛莉亚  让你受伤是我最不愿见到的事
Gloria, that's the last thing I meant to happen.
你只是口头说说  你不是真的明白
You're just saying that. You don't really understand.
我是不明白  抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
最不想让别人觉得自己说话
Hell, I'm the last guy who wants to make somebody
很蠢的人  就是我了
feel like they sound stupid.
我有没有跟你提过  以前住我家附近
Did I ever tell you about the little boy
讲话结巴的那个小男孩
from my neighborhood who stuttered?
他为此很自卑
He was real self-conscious about it.
哪个孩子不会呢
What kid wouldn't be?
上课时  老师向他提问
At school, when the teacher would ask him a question,
他很努力想说出答案
he tried so hard to get the words out,
但就是说不出来
but it just wouldn't come.
其他孩子都看着他
Rest of the kids stared at him,
他反而更结巴了
which only made the stuttering worse.
他们在背后笑话他
They'd whisper behind his back and laugh.
最后发展到老师叫他回答问题时
Finally, got to the point when the teacher called on him
他即便知道答案
to answer a question, even if he knew the answer,
也说  "我不会"
he'd just say, "I don't know."
然后老师就会摇摇头  说
Then the teacher would shake his head and say,
"下次要更努力学习  杰"
"Next time, study harder, Jay."
你就是那个小男孩
You were that little kid?
好可怜
So sad.
你那时一定很难过
That must have been very hard for you.
的确
It was.
车停好了
We're parked.
好了  电影快开始了
Okay, the movie's about to start.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我有好多年没想起过那件事了
Man, I haven't thought about that in years.
真的很感人
That was really moving.
因为这才是正确的讲故事方式
'Cause that's how you tell a story.
你好  你能不能在五分钟之内
Hi, could you bring out the birthday cake
把生日蛋糕拿出来
in like five, minutes?
没问题  你想要我们唱生日歌吗
Sure, do you want the whole song and everything?
-能唱就最好了  -我问你纯粹是因为
- Oh, that would be great. - I only ask because
-我们不想唱  -好吧  谢谢
- we don't love doing it. - Okay, thanks.
你好吗  小寿星
Hey. ‭So, birthday boy,
心情如何啊
how you feeling?
说实话  有点紧张
Um, a little nervous, actually.
为什么
Why?
其实吧
Uh, well.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
海莉  我今早醒来时
Haley, when I woke up this morning,
就有股浓烈的感情涌上心头
I just had this feeling.
我知道这很突然
And I know this is sudden,
但是如同每个中大型频道的天气预报员
but like any mid-to-large market weatherman,
我相信自己的直觉
I trust my instincts.
可能也和我快到45岁有点关系
And it might have something to do with turning 45,
但今天我的直觉告诉我  不要再浪费时间
but today my instincts told me not to wait another second
我想和我爱的女人共度余生
to spend the rest of my life with the woman I love.
海莉·格温多林·邓菲  你愿意嫁给我吗
Haley Gwendolyn Dunphy, will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.
-我愿意嫁给你  -真的吗  你愿意嫁给我
- Yes, I'll marry you. - Really? You will?
真的
Yeah!
就是感觉对了  你懂吗
It just feels right, you know?
我不想要想太多
I don't want to over-think it.
我喜欢的就是你这点
That's what I love about you.
你任何事都不会想太多
You don't over-think anything.
你让我成为了世上最幸福的男人
Oh, you've made me the happiest man in the world.
我不知道这话怎么说才不会显得贪财
I don't know how to say this without sounding superficial,
但我想好好看看这戒指
but I need a closer look at this ring.
没问题  坐  坐吧
Yeah, sit down, sit down.
这是我奶奶传下来的
It was my grandmother's.
她当年在大萧条时期时把戒指
She hid it in her hollowed-out wooden foot
藏在挖空的木头假腿里
during the Great Depression.
震惊  我奶奶居然在大朋友圈
So crazy my grandmother's on Snapchat.
太美了
It's beautiful.
我这样不会破坏了惊喜吧
I didn't ruin the surprise, did I?
我本来是想装没事到吃完晚餐
I mean, I was trying to act normal through dinner.
但我实在藏不住内心的紧张
I just couldn't hide how nervous I was.
我想粉丝们走近跟我说话时  也是这心情吧
It's how I imagine fans feel when they come up and meet me.
没破坏  我完全没预料到
No, I didn't expect it at all.
我本来以为你紧张是因为
I just thought you were nervous because the light's
灯光打在了你右脸上
on the right side of your face.
对啊  你看看我
Yeah. Oh, look at me --
嘴都不自觉在笑了
I can't stop smiling. ‭Yeah!
我通常都是把笑容留到镜头前
Usually I like to save my smiles for on-camera
因为这样会显得笑容比较真
because they come off more real that way.
但为此而笑太值了
Oh, yeah. ‭But this is worth it.
-奇了怪了  -怎么了
- That's odd. - ‭What's wrong?
下雨了
It's raining.
我没有预料到  我报了今晚晴朗呢
I didn't predict that -- I called for clear skies tonight.
我们要不要点个香槟来庆祝一下
Ooh, should we order some champagne to celebrate?
真不敢相信我的预报错了
I can't believe my forecast was wrong.
别太苛责自己了
Oh, don't beat yourself up about it.
我的气象预报应用也没预测到下雨啊
If it helps, my weather app didn't predict rain either.
-你的什么  -没什么
- Your what? - ‭Nothing.
天啊  看看那大风
My God, look at those winds.
这起码是10级的暴风啊
They must register at least a 10 on the Beaufort Scale.
看看那些没关上的天窗
Think of all the sun roofs left open.
想想那些刚吹好的发型塌下来
Think of all the freshly blown-out hair de-volumizing.
我怎么能没预判到这个呢
How could I not see this coming?
雷纳
Rainer.
这是我今天唯一错判的事吗
Is this the only thing I was off about today?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
海莉  别自欺欺人了  我没有好好想清楚
Well, let's face it, Haley. I did not think this through.
我们婚后住哪里啊
I mean, where are we gonna live?
我家只有一个步入式衣帽间  它会维持是我的
My place only has one walk-in closet, which would stay mine.
我的女儿会对我们结婚这事有何想法
And how's my daughter gonna feel about us getting married?
你会想要有孩子吗
Are you gonna want to have children?
我还有办法播种吗
Can I even have more children?
我去照过很多次日光浴床呢
I've spent a lot of time in tanning beds.
我觉得你有点懵了
Um, I think you're spinning a little.
听我说  有时候当我在重新整理衣柜时
Look, sometimes when I'm reorganizing my closet,
我也会有手足无措感  觉得好像永远收不完
I feel overwhelmed, like I'm never gonna get through it all.
所以我逼自己把事情分成一小块一小块
So I force myself to look at things in smaller sections.
比如一次整理五双鞋子
I arrange five pairs of shoes at a time.
12小时后  我就完事啦
12 hours later, I'm done.
所以我们也来这么做
So, that's what we'll do.
我们把事情分成5年  5年来处理
We'll take things five years at a time.
-5年后我就要50岁啦  -什么
- In five years, I'll be 50. - What?
你本来觉得45加5等于多少
What did you think 45 plus 5 was?
今天之前我一直当你是44岁
Well, until today, you were 44,
然后我洗脑了自己你四舍五入是40岁
which I had basically convinced myself was 40,
结果突然就成了50岁  四舍五入就是60岁
and now suddenly we're talking about 50, which is basically 60.
你有什么好恐慌的
Why are you panicking?
我才是不容再有一次失败婚姻的人
I'm the one who can't mess up another marriage.
你看  第一次婚姻失败  没关系
I mean, you mess up the first one, fine.
表现不好能重来  但第二次又失败
It's a mulligan. But the second one fails,
我就是婚姻失败的凶手了
and suddenly I'm the problem.
我也就失去了成为
I lose my chance at being the spokesperson
韩国蓝台风能量饮料代言人的资格
for Blue Monsoon Korean Energy Drink.
让我们先缓口气
Let's just take a breath.
稍微有点惊慌失措是很正常的
It's natural to freak out a little bit.
毕竟我们在做的是一生的承诺
We're making a lifetime commitment.
我们要一辈子永不分离
We're going to be together forever.
就我跟你俩人  永不分离
Just you and me. Forever.
你这话重复说了
You just said that.
我知道啊
I know.
因为...  因为这太棒了
Because -- because it's great.
每个女都孩梦寐以求  对吧
That's what every girl wants, right?
的确  我还是花季少女  而世界上
I mean, sure, I'm still really young and there's obviously
也还有许多我想先去做完
so much more I thought I'd do before I tied myself down
再跟某个人定下来的事情
to one person for the rest of my life.
但有谁会真的觉得自己准备好结婚了啊
But does anyone ever truly feel ready to get married?
大概吧
I mean, probably.
-海莉  -但我也不是要死掉
- Haley. - But it's not like I'm dying.
只不过是不会再单身而已
I just won't be single anymore.
再也不会跟人初次约会
I'll won't ever go on a first date again.
再也不会跟人初吻
I won't ever have a first kiss.
再也不会在DJ台附近跳舞
I won't ever dance near a deejay booth
然后在心里祈祷有人欣赏
hoping someone will like what they see
然后愿意载我回家
and offer me a ride home.
天啊  是...  是我的问题
Oh, my -- is it - is it me?
还是这餐厅里超热
Or is it just crazy hot in here?
麻烦谁开一下窗子可以吗
Can somebody open a window, please?
不  他们不能开  如我所没预料到的
No, no, they can't because, as I did not predict,
外面正在刮风下雨
it's raining outside.
我的手指肿起来了
Ew, my finger is swelling up.
为什么你奶奶的大萧条戒指这么紧啊
Oh, why is your grandmother's Depression ring so tight?
把黄油给我
Give me that butter.
■
微信扫描
上方二维码
关注TV哔
一起哔哔哔
来  我来帮忙你
Here, let me help you with that.
我拔啦
I got it.
-天啊  对不起  -没  没关系
- Ow! ‭Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. ‭- Nope, it's okay.
我没事
I'm fine.
至少戒指拔下来了
At least the ring came off.
对啊  感觉好多了
Yeah, um, feels better.
听我说  或许你是对的
Look, um, maybe you're right.
或许我们应该重新琢磨一下结婚这事
Maybe we should rethink this whole marriage thing.
我不记得说过这话啊
I don't remember saying that.
很明显你心里还有疑虑
It's clear you're having doubts.
我们俩都还有
We both are.
我们就先继续交往再看看吧
Let's just keep dating and see where it goes.
我不想要这样
I don't want to do that.
的确  的确我不太敢作出承诺
I mean, I -- clearly, I've had some commitment issues,
我也知道我刚才短暂的恐慌了一下
and I know I had a momentary freak out there,
但我...  我不知道你...
but I was -- I had no idea that you w--
海莉  我知道这很不公平
Haley, I know it's unfair.
或许我是有些期望你会对我们的感情
I guess I was just hoping you'd be sure enough
有足够的信心
for the both of us.
是啊
You're right.
这样的确不公平
It isn't fair.
所以你真的要退还给我吗
You're really giving this back?
只是暂时的
Just for now.
海莉  我已经45岁了
Haley, I'm 45 years old.
我不想要单纯交往再看情况
I-I don't want to just date and see where things go.
我的人生已经过了那阶段了
That's not where I am in my life.
你想说什么
What are you saying?
我觉得我俩都是一个意思
Well, I think we're both saying it.
-* 生... *  -别  先别
- ♪ Ha-- ♪ - No, no, don't.
太好了
Oh, good.
您想吹熄蜡烛[分手]吗
Do you want to blow out the candles?
先生
Sir.
怎么  发生什么事了
What, what happened?
我们到达拉斯了吗
Are we in Dallas yet?
已经离开达拉斯了  现在在中美洲的小岛上
No, we left Dallas. We're in Turks and Caicos.
我们需要清机舱了
We need to clean the plane.
什么
What?
你有任何我们到达拉斯的记忆吗
Do you remember being in Dallas?
没有  估计是直接睡过去了
No, we must have slept through it.
你戴着一顶牛仔帽
You're wearing an cowboy hat.
你也是
So are you.
-这是什么  -我们好像不该拥有这玩意吧
- What is this? - I don't think we're supposed to have that.
貌似我好像穿了个环
So, it appears I've gotten a piercing.
什么
What?
"默里"
"Murray."
为什么你的手臂上写了"默里"
Why does your arm say "Murray"?
这是谁的狗啊
Who... whose dog is this?
您这话是什么意思
What do you mean "whose dog"?
当时您说不能带他就不登机
You refused to board without him.
我说了吗
I did?
好吧  咱们走
Okay, well, let's go.
我不记得我的袋子有这么重啊
I don't remember my bag being this heavy.